

### **PERSONAL**

- Name Yi Ting Lan
- Mobile 0921763276
- 🍹 Portfolio www.delphinelan.com

#### LANGUAGES

**English** Japanese Mandrain Native Taiwanese Advanced

#### **INTERESTS**

- Painting
- Reading

# YI TING LAN



Yi Ting Lan is a Taiwan designer specialising in UI Design, Graphic Design, and Digital Design. I am a dependable team worker in the company.

Even if I have never been exposed to work or software I never stop learned and get myself into the situation quickly. I continue to improve the necessary skills in the workplace, and also like to collect relevant information.

I also hope that will be more development in the future. I have a very positive attitude and full of ideals and ambitions for my work.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

Aug 2019 - Present

### Senior Visual Designer

Anue 鉅亨金融科技股份有限公司(鉅亨網), Taipei

- Internal Website and APP UI Design by sketch.
- Advertising Banner and Campaingn page production .
- ★ Hao.cnyes: This project is a social media platform focusing on financial management. My work is cross-platform UI/UX design including APP and RWD WEB and CMS management system.
- ★ UI revised design of the news website.
- ★ UI design of the company's B2B cooperation webpage and campaign page then complete all of this by html and css.

Jun 2015 - Jul 2019

### Web Designer

AMC 空中美語, Taipei

- Internal RWD Campaign Pages Design based on the ability of html and css.
- DM > POSTER Design based on the ability of photoshop and illustrator.
- ★ The company's official website: UI design and complete by html.
- ★ The course selection system : UI designed and complete by html, then cooperation with RD to connection the background information.

Apr 2012 - May 2015 Graphic Designer

風尚國際廣告事業有限公司, Taipei

- DM > POSTER Design based on the ability of photoshop and illustrator.
- Producing vedio by After effects and premiere.
- ★ The exhibition booklet and bookcover design of the TAITRA.
- ★ The exhibition newspaper of the TIS (Taipei IN Style Taipei Charm Show).

Oct 2010 - Aug 2011 Graphic Designer

偉氏國際有限公司, Taipei

- DM > POSTER Design based on the ability of photoshop and illustrator.

## EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS

Sep 2006 - Jul 2010 Bachelor degree of Digital Multimedia Arts

Shih Hsin University, SHU, Taipei

3D Building and animation design skills

- Creative strategy animation planning.
- Producing visual effects Video.

## SKILLS

Sketch	Experienced	*	*	*	*	*
Adobe XD	Experienced	*	*	*	*	*
Adobe Photoshop	Experienced	*	*	*	*	*
Adobe Illustrator	Experienced	*	*	*	*	*
html	Skillful	*	*	*	*	*
css	Skillful	*	*	*	*	*

## **COURSES**

Apr 2021 - Present Google UX Design

Google Career Certificates from Coursera

Apr 2021 - Jun 2021 An Introduction of Watercolor Painting

NTNU Extension, School of Continuing Education

Sep 2020 - Feb 2021 An Introduction of Oil Painting

NTNU Extension, School of Continuing Education